<browser-action actionType="BrowserSelectOption" isHit="false"
    name="Select option _" uid="c06bd8af-5193-4676-a830-19be1170980a">
    <description>Select an option from the html select element identified by the selector.
You can specify several options if the select element has the 'multiple' attribute, or you can specify none to clear the selection.

Possible parameters are:&#xd;
- selector (required): The selector is a string that point to the elements in the page. Several types of selector are supported: text, CSS, XPath...
	You can specify several selectors by adding multiple "selector" parameters to this action. The targeted element will match any of the selectors (OR operator).&#xd;
- options[0].text (optional): Select the option with a matching text. Multiple options can be selected by adding more parameters with a different index.&#xd;
- options[0].value (optional): Select the option with a matching index. Multiple options can be selected by adding more parameters with a different index.&#xd;
- options[0].index (optional): Select the option with a matching value. Multiple options can be selected by adding more parameters with a different index.&#xd;
- timeout (optional): Forces the timeout for that action in ms. By default the OpenBrowser defaultTimeout is used.&#xd;
- frameIndex (optional): Frame index. Takes priority over frameName parameter.&#xd;
- frameName (optional): Frame name.&#xd;
- waitForNavigation.url (optional): URL pattern targeted, ex:http://tricentis.com/.* . The URL being navigated to must match this pattern. Enables a wait for page navigation after this action has been executed.&#xd;
- waitForNavigation.timeout (optional): If applicable, the navigation must occur within the specified timeout in ms. By default the OpenBrowser defaultNavigationTimeout is used. Enables a wait for page navigation after this action has been executed.&#xd;
- waitForNavigation.until (optional): Allowed values are : LOAD, DOMCONTENTLOADED, NETWORKIDLE, COMMIT. Default value is LOAD. The navigation will be considered done when the specified state is reached. Enables a wait for page navigation after this action has been executed.</description>
    <custom-action-parameter name="selector" type="TEXT" value="[name=&quot;l&quot;]"/>
    <custom-action-parameter name="selector" type="TEXT" value="form > select:nth-child(1)"/>
    <custom-action-parameter name="options[0].text" type="TEXT" value="ភាសាខ្មែរ"/>
    <custom-action-parameter name="waitForNavigation.url" type="TEXT" value=".*"/>
    <responsePageFileDescription>recorded-responses/res_c06bd8af-5193-4676-a830-19be1170980a</responsePageFileDescription>
    <screenshotFileDescription>recorded-screenshots/sc_c06bd8af-5193-4676-a830-19be1170980a.jpg</screenshotFileDescription>
    <embedded-action>6bf0e286-9758-449c-9199-2f3c87e4324e</embedded-action>
</browser-action>
